<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kevin Blog: A Developer's Journey through Web Technologies</title><link>https://duykhoa.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Kevin Blog: A Developer's Journey through Web Technologies</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 08:07:22 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://duykhoa.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>User Authentication With Springboot using local database</title><link>https://duykhoa.github.io/posts/user-authentication-with-springboot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 08:07:22 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://duykhoa.github.io/posts/user-authentication-with-springboot/</guid><description>This post is a short tutorial of how to configure the spring security for your app to support user authentication using local database.
Introduction 🔗In Spring Boot, there is no plug-and-play like other frameworks. To get the user authentication working, you need to write some code to glue the required components working together. Spring Security was designed to be flexible with multiple authentication/authorization strategies.
Overview design 🔗Servlet Filter chains 🔗 source from SpringIO</description></item><item><title>Tracking Email Activity Ses</title><link>https://duykhoa.github.io/posts/tracking-email-activity-ses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 16:41:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://duykhoa.github.io/posts/tracking-email-activity-ses/</guid><description>Introduction 🔗The email sending function is a common feature found in almost every website. For developers, AWS SES (AWS Simple Email Service) is a popular choice, particularly when the website is hosted on the AWS cloud. Although AWS SES doesn&amp;rsquo;t directly support email activity tracking, it does offer the possibility to create custom tracking features by integrating with other AWS services. In this post, I will explain how to build an application that tracks email sending activities using SNS HTTPs endpoint.</description></item><item><title>Setup local domain with self-signed SSL certificate</title><link>https://duykhoa.github.io/posts/local-domain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 22:51:16 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://duykhoa.github.io/posts/local-domain/</guid><description>Objective 🔗The local domain are helpful to setup the connection between the frontend and backend on the development machine. It is also a common solution when the actual address and port is difficult to remember. In this post, I will explain how to set up the local domain and config the SSL certificate on the MacOS laptop.
Softwares required 🔗In order to config the local domain name and issue the SSL cert, we&amp;rsquo;ll need these tools installed:</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://duykhoa.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 15:00:15 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://duykhoa.github.io/about/</guid><description>Hello world!
I&amp;rsquo;m a Software Engineer with passion in the Devops site. I have contributed multiple successes of various business domains, which includes the private banking, ride-hailing and automotive.
I&amp;rsquo;ve used some Web technologies, which are varied by the work requirements. For the last 2 years, I have insensitively developed the GRPC and GraphQL micro-services using Typescript.
I have advocated in building a high reusability codebase with the support Monorepo and Trunk Base Development, put together with the internal tools to provide a pleasant development experience.</description></item><item><title>A project specific command-line</title><link>https://duykhoa.github.io/posts/a-cli-showcase/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 22:59:40 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://duykhoa.github.io/posts/a-cli-showcase/</guid><description>We have a Nodejs monorepo project that is the place where we develop the code of all applications. The inspiration behind using monorepo is focusing on improving developer productivity. Having our own commandline is an idea to further enhance the productivity by providing a simpler way to develop the code.
In this post, we will walk through the use cases of the tool and how does it help the team.</description></item><item><title>A Simple Infrastructure</title><link>https://duykhoa.github.io/posts/a-simple-infras/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 09:55:09 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://duykhoa.github.io/posts/a-simple-infras/</guid><description>Nowadays, there are a variety of choices to deploy a website. Developers could choose a container service like Heroku, go with the most trendy infrastructure of choice with Kubernetes, or use the Serverless strategy to run the website without the need of setting up the server on their own. However, configuring a web server is no longer rocket surgery with the modern DevOps technologies and the revolution of the Cloud providers.</description></item></channel></rss>