<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Devops on Kevin Blog: A Developer's Journey through Web Technologies</title><link>https://duykhoa.github.io/tags/devops/</link><description>Recent content in Devops on Kevin Blog: A Developer's Journey through Web Technologies</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 22:51:16 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://duykhoa.github.io/tags/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setup local domain with self-signed SSL certificate</title><link>https://duykhoa.github.io/posts/local-domain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 22:51:16 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://duykhoa.github.io/posts/local-domain/</guid><description>Objective 🔗The local domain are helpful to setup the connection between the frontend and backend on the development machine. It is also a common solution when the actual address and port is difficult to remember. In this post, I will explain how to set up the local domain and config the SSL certificate on the MacOS laptop.
Softwares required 🔗In order to config the local domain name and issue the SSL cert, we&amp;rsquo;ll need these tools installed:</description></item><item><title>A project specific command-line</title><link>https://duykhoa.github.io/posts/a-cli-showcase/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 22:59:40 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://duykhoa.github.io/posts/a-cli-showcase/</guid><description>We have a Nodejs monorepo project that is the place where we develop the code of all applications. The inspiration behind using monorepo is focusing on improving developer productivity. Having our own commandline is an idea to further enhance the productivity by providing a simpler way to develop the code.
In this post, we will walk through the use cases of the tool and how does it help the team.</description></item><item><title>A Simple Infrastructure</title><link>https://duykhoa.github.io/posts/a-simple-infras/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 09:55:09 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://duykhoa.github.io/posts/a-simple-infras/</guid><description>Nowadays, there are a variety of choices to deploy a website. Developers could choose a container service like Heroku, go with the most trendy infrastructure of choice with Kubernetes, or use the Serverless strategy to run the website without the need of setting up the server on their own. However, configuring a web server is no longer rocket surgery with the modern DevOps technologies and the revolution of the Cloud providers.</description></item></channel></rss>